(Susan:)Stop trying to be
the cool dad;
(Susan:)you have a shirt
with our cat's picture on it.
(Wyatt:)Anyway, we're here, slugger.
(Howard:)That's great, now they
know where I live.
(Raj:)What are you talking about?
(Raj:)They've always known
where you live.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, if you want to go
off the grid,
(Bernadette:)you have to move out
of your mother's house.
(Raj:)Can we take a moment
to discuss
(Raj:)that I just lied
to the government for you?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Howard:)I would not have
done that for you.
(Bernadette:)Howard, please just call
the man, see what he wants.
(Howard:)All right, all right.
(Sheldon:)Hey,
(Raj:)make sure you tell him that
you weren't home when he came by
(Raj:)and that your Indian friend
gave you the message
(Raj:)the moment
you stepped through the door.
(Howard:)Yes, hello.
Uh,
(Howard:)this is Howard Wolowitz
for Colonel Richard Williams.
(Raj:)Oh, I take it back,
don't mention me.
(Howard:)Hi, Colonel Williams,
how can I help you?
(Howard:)What? Oh, uh, yes,
he is from India.